Oh, hello there, sir
And welcome to my monster brothel
where we cater to customers who are looking
for a more than ordinary experience with a woman
I don't think I've seen you here before
and I remember the face of every man I see
This is your first time coming here, isn't it
No need to be embarrassed
Everyone has their first time at a brothel at some point
No shame in that Why
yes, I am a succubus What gave it away
My horns
My swishing tail
My wings
I'm just teasing you
sir
There's no need to be embarrassed about any desires or thoughts in my brothel
Here As I said, we cater to every kind of taste and desire you could imagine
No matter how deprived they may be considered outside these doors
Nothing is off--limits in Zai
So
what kind of experience were you looking for here
What kind of girl were you interested in
And how much experience have..
Oh
say..
Sir, I hope it isn't too proddy for me to ask, but..
Are you perhaps a virgin
Well, succubus are just kind of able to tell and
smell the level of sexual experience on a man
And you happen to have a very fresh scent on you
Am
I right in assuming so
Come now
there's no need to be shy in admitting it
I see
So you are
Well, we have plenty of girls here who would be
perfect for a first--timer like yourself
So, if you'll just follow me I'll go get my book
that has all the different girls who are available right now
all you have to do is point at the one you like
I'll send you to your room and she should be there shortly after
so if you just follow me down the hall
you know, you don't need to pretend not to look at me, right
do you think I wear this revealing lingerie
because I don't want people to look at me
I wear it because I get wet
when people stare at my breasts and my ass
So, are you acting like you're trying not to look at me
as actually getting me wet
Oh, you stud
Are you sure you're really a virgin
Getting a succubus wet just by looking at her
Now, here we are
So, as you can see from this book
we have categorized all the different types
of girls we have into different sections
based on their experience and expertise
along with pictures of each of them
So, what kind of girl are you looking for
A werewolf
A harpy
A slime girl
We have just about every kind of girl you can think of here
I even have a ghost girl who can possess
you and combine her orgasms with your own
Oh, a succubus
We absolutely have a list of different succubi to choose from
And I can point out a few who would absolutely love to get their hands on a cute
delicious virgin such as yourself And I don't mean to display favoritism
but there truly aren't any other type of
girls in the world who can fuck and suck like a succubus can
So, which of these would you like to choose
Do you prefer the older
big--breasted males
Or perhaps you prefer the smaller and younger girls
Hmm
See anyone who catches your attention
Or, with the way you keep taking glances at me
wouldn't you like to choose me
the brothel owner herself
to be your escort
Oh
I was only teasing, but..
was I perhaps right
You would actually prefer me
I'm sorry, sir
Though, I am a succubus
I..
I do run this place
And I usually make it a policy not to sleep with customers myself
Oh, please don't look so disappointed
It just..
makes you look..
so much cuter
I..
Okay
Why don't you head upstairs to your room
Room 24
Just wait there and I'll see what I can do
It might be a bit of an extra wait
so just be patient and enjoy some of the refreshments that are laid out there
okay
Also, you should find a very soft robe hanging on the back of the door
if you wouldn't mind
You could slip out of your street clothes
and into that in the meantime
I think you'll find it'll be much comfortable for you
Off you go, darling
Hello
It's me
Sorry for the wait
Nice and comfortable on the bed already
And I see that robe fits you comfortably as well Well, I
had to freshen up a bit and change into a robe myself
so this really isn't something I ever normally do
just so, you know
but we do pride ourselves on having outstanding satisfaction with our customers
and
well, I don't know
Well, I suppose I just found you particularly cute and enticing
so just for tonight
I'll indulge both you and myself
and I'll do it
I'll be the one taking your virginity
so just how much experience have you had with a girl outside sex
of course
i see that isn't really much, well
why don't i just dim the lights a bit and light a few candles
i can tell you're nervous and i want this
first experience to be as nice and enjoyable for you as possible
I sense you are quite attracted to me
But also sense something else
Do I make you nervous
Is it because I'm a succubus
Or because I have so much experience when it comes to matters such as this
I see
Well, though, I have slept with more men and women than I can count
as all succubi have
one thing you should understand is that, as a succubus
I view every time I have sex as almost like a first time for me
If it's performance or impressing me that has you worried
then you needn't worry about it
I plan to view this experience with you as just experiencing it with you alone
not with those I've had before you
Besides, I'll be guiding you through it
every step of the way
Now then
I'll just go ahead and remove my robe right now
You look pleased with what you see
Do you enjoy my naked form
I'll admit, when you came here and couldn't take your eyes off of me
it got me more wet than normal
With the way you were pretending not to look
So now
I'll just slowly make my way up to you on the bed
Until..
I'm straddling you
Just like this
Enjoying the view from down there
My breasts are quite nice looking
aren't they
Did you know that the breasts of succubi always remain perky
Our pussy is always tight
No one knows how to use their mouth as well as a succubus can, either
Men have said our mouths feel just as good as our pussies
And that our suction is unreal
And whenever my tail starts swishing around like this
It usually means I'm very
very excited I'm sure you can tell Can you feel it
The heat of my pussy going through your ropes The wetness
The ways succubi are far hotter inside compared to any human girls as well
well, i can already feel you hardening against me, that's good
nothing turns me on more than a man getting excited by my charm
well, no need to lay there with your arms at your side
touch me, feel me
starting with my hips
i can tell you like them
enjoying how wide they they feel
And how soft and smooth my skin feels
I'm sure this is the first time you're really getting to touch a woman this much
Are you surprised at how soft we are compared to you
My breasts
Of course, you may touch them
Grab them and knead them as much as you like
No need to worry about being gentle
I can assure you that we succubi are very hard to break
I hate them in your hands
just like that
Explore me
They're quite soft and squishy, aren't they
And I can't believe it
but you're already starting to make my nipples go so hard
Yes, you are
Feel them for yourself
Try rolling them between the ends of your fingers
Yes, just like that
Goodness, I must be honest with you
I wouldn't ever gotten my nipples this hard so quickly before
I can't remember the last time I was given goosebumps
I so wanna show you what else there is to experience
But first
I'll just lean over Like this And take your adorable face in my hands Now
I'll..
just..
try to follow the rhythm my mouth moves at
My, you're actually quite good at that
But if I didn't know any better
I'd say you've had a lot of practice
Pushing your tongue into my mouth certainly took my breath away
Now, I'm just going to open the front of your robes a bit
Oh, my handsome looking chest
And now I'm going to start kissing my way down
I love those little sighs you're making
Do you like the way my lips feel on your chest
I certainly love the way your chest feels against my lips
You seem to be pitching quite a tent now
So, I'm just going to open your robes and give it some air
oh, this is quite an impressive cock to think
you've been hiding this thing inside your robes all this time, well
since you're still so new to all this
i think, um
i think i'm just going to start off giving you a blowjob for now
if that's okay with you
the night is still very young and And..
you have me the entire time
Good
And don't worry about me
For a succubus
drinking down cum gives us almost as much
pleasure as having an orgasm ourselves
But I can't have you cumming too soon
So, as a precaution
I'm going to take my tail and wrap it around the base of your cock
Just like this
That should help make sure your cock behaves
I can tell how badly you want it
if I just lean down and blow on it
and
breathe down on it
Feeling my hot breath run all the way down your cock
turning into a tickling breeze on your belly
It just makes you ache to be taken into my mouth
doesn't it
Hehe, you are so adorable
Alright, I won't make you wait any longer
So, I'll just start with some soft kisses
right on the head
I
don't know if it's just because you're such an adorable virgin
but your pre--cum is some of the sweetest I've ever tasted
I'm very serious, darling
and now I want to get a better taste
because I cannot wait I can't wait any longer, myself
Darling, your cock tastes so good
I honestly can't remember the last time I've tasted a cock this good before
oh, smell
taste such so delicious
look at you
making such adorable noises and moving around
it's a good thing my tail is wrapped around your cock
Or you may have come already And I can't have that
No I want the pressure And longing To build up So when you finally explode
You'll absolutely give me as much cum as you possibly can
I'll get the satisfaction of drinking down every fucking drop
And I'll get the satisfaction of drinking
down every drop While I watch you writhe on the bed with pleasure
Thank you
the way you let out that sigh shiver
every time i swirl my tongue around the head of your cock like this
how are you enjoying your very first blowjob
i can tell you right now
no human woman would ever be able to make you feel this good with just her mouth
Only a succubus
Specifically
only a succubus like me Could ever make you feel this good with her mouth
I'm going to take you even deeper into my throat
So hold on
darling
Oh, my God
it's been a long time since i've been that
enthusiastic about deep throwing a cock
i must say the effect you have on me has me rather perplexed Well, no matter
I can tell your cock is on the verge of exploding
So hard and so swollen
So, I'll show you mercy
And finally, unwrap my tail from the base of your poor cock
And I'm going to take you back into my mouth again
Oh
my ear cum
I know there has been your life
I just shoot that gun Into my mouth And I burn your head I want
every drop of you
Please I love you all so much
I love
you all so much the very, very
very
very, very, very
very, very
very happy
and this is me
ah
and
this is me, and this is me
and all of the people that I have supported and that I have raised
and that I've loved
and that I have Do we have to draw
well, darling, i must commend you out of all the different ones i've tasted
your cock and your cum are by far one of the sweetest
in the way
you were thrashing around as i drank down
every drop was just about the cutest thing i've ever seen
i'm so glad i bent the rules that i could
take care of you myself if i had let one of my other girls do it
and later found out just how sweet you tasted and how cute you were
well, i never would have forgiven myself
i'll just lay myself down here next to you while you ride the high down
and
then, once you're ready
i have a little trick you need to suck you by
that will help shorten up that pesky refractory period of yours
Because, having gotten a taste of you
I find myself having only had my appetite wet
I honestly have never wanted a man more than I have you
and I don't think I'll be satisfied until
I've completely taken your virginity for my own
i've given you your first blowjob
but it's not enough, not nearly enough
don't you even worry about the cost
because i don't plan to charge you for any of this
Oh, no, this
this isn't about business This is just about pleasure
And me getting what I want Giving you what you need
And it's going to take most of tonight
at least
So, my darling Prepare yourself for round two
Had a moment to catch your breath
how was that for a first blow--job no other
mouth out there would have felt as good as that
and i must say i don't think any other girl
could have swallowed all that oh so sweet cum you were putting out earlier
Had I missed even a single drop
it would bring shame to me as a succubus
And, of course, if I were anyone but a succubus
then our night would have ended at that blowjob
And you would have gone home feeling no doubt satisfied
but still wishing the night could have lasted longer
How fortunate, however
that I am a succubus
because, as i said, i can make it go away
that satisfied feeling of being drained
the flaccidness and sensitivity on the head of your cock
i can turn it all around and make it feel like you haven't come in weeks
like you're one of those poor
misguarded souls who take part
Pardon, that no--fap November event
Ugh
Mind you
most succubi hate the month of November
Specifically for that reason
But they also love it
Because it's the easiest time of year to get our sustenance
You have no idea how easy it is to get a man to give in to our kind
And a month where they purposefully deprive themselves makes it oh so much easier
But, I'm rambling now, so I digress, how about it, want me to do it
do you want me to get your cock all hard and back up again
so you can gift me your virginity
and then cream into my tight little pussy for the rest of the night
that's my boy
so the way I do it is quite simple
It's an aphrodisiac that's in my saliva
All I have to do is kiss you and give your cock a little attention as well
And that's all it takes
So, are you ready
Good, because I am
Now, open your mouth and stick out your tongue
Yes, just like that
Now I'm just going to straddle you
and slowly start leaning down, like this
Like seeing my tits hanging down
Mmm, good
I love the way you look at me
And next I'll just..
Already starting to feel it
aren't you
That feeling of desire returning That starts at your head
Making your cheeks feel hot Before slowly working its way down your body
Eventually it will get to your cock
In fact
it looks like it's starting to get a little rise out of you already
But, we're going to speed things up a little bit
So, I'm just going to move my way down your chest
Down this beautiful chest
Such a cute--looking belly button
What if I just..
That's such a cute little reaction
You're starting to feel a little more flesh now
aren't you
My line of kisses
leaving behind little wet spots to get you even more horny
And next..
oh, this gorgeous and wonderful cock of yours
it gives out cum that's just so sweet and to die for
i'll just
oh, look how quickly it's growing
i can already taste the pre--cum
that means your balls are already starting to fill up with more cum again
can you see that growing aching coming on
Oh, so cute
You're just so cute
The sound you're making and the look on your face
they all tell me yes
And here we are
All hurt again and ready to go
Oh, didn't I tell you that it would be easy
And now you look all backed up again
and your cock looks all swollen and purple
And if I get up just a little bit, you can see, my pussy
how dripping wet it is
how much it needs your cock
what if i just start rubbing your cock through the lips of my pussy
like this
you feel how wet you've made me
how much you've made me long for you
I need you
I've never needed the cock of a man like you in as long as I can remember
Your cum
Your honey sweet cum
I want you to paint my insides white with it
But I want to hear you say it
I want to hear you say you need me as much as I need you
It's not even because I want to tease you
I've never been this turned on in my life
I just, I just, I really need to hear you
I need to hear it from myself
Say it
Say it, please
Please
thank you, thank you
okay
it won't make us wait any longer
i'll just guide you in
that's
it
i'll keep moving myself down on you
god, the way this cock of yours stretches me open is just unreal Real- B-
Oh
Okay..
I got you..
All the way in..
Hehe..
Congratulations..
You're no longer a virgin..
Mmm..
But goodness..
Are you sure you're really human
Making a succubus pace for herself like this..
Okay..
Ooh..
I'm going to start moving now..
So put your hands on my hips
Yeah
And just like that
And just enjoy it
Enjoy spreading me open
And come whenever you want
Fuck, oh fuck
it feels so good Your cock just spreads me all the way to the back
I'm so glad I'm doing this
I'm so glad I bent the rules and took you for myself
I honestly don't know if any other girls would have been able to handle this
Maybe one of the others suck you by
but there's no fucking way I'm letting them have you
I don't care if this cock ends up marking me as yours
I want to be marked as yours, please
just dig your fingers into my hips, just like that
squeeze as hard as you want
it hurts so good
you don't mind if I dig my nails into you a little bit
do you
I need something to grab onto
I might end up scratching you
I might end up marking you a bit
that's okay, right
oh good, I'm glad, I'm so glad
I can feel your cock pulsating as it's going in
And out of me, I just can't get enough
I love
the feeling of bringing my hips down so hard
And on the head of your cock
it's my cervix
Do you like seeing the way my tits bounce
Reach up and grab them
Break them as yours
And bruise them, please
Just like that
Yes, yes, just like that
I've
been going for my nipples when I didn't have to tell you
Fuck, you're such a fucking natural at this
Oh, fuck
Here, I'm just going to lean down
I'll keep going
I want to kiss you again
Open your mouth and stick out your tongue again
Please, please
You're such a good kisser
Even with my long tongue
You're still wrestling in submission
If you buck your hips into me like that It's going to make me
It's too good It's too good
You're hitting me at just Too good of an angle
You're going to make me cum Much before you are
This is the way your cock keeps going In and out of me
The way you hit me with the back of your hips Just like that Fuck
You're gonna make me fucking cum while I'm
cream and cream all over your fucking cock
I'm gonna cream, I'm gonna do it
I can't believe I'm gonna fucking cum before you do I'm just gonna cum
No cum yet
no cum yet Please, please, I don't want this to be over yet
please I have to cum first, please
I have to cum first Just this once
please
Oh, it's so good
I love creaming all over your cock
Feel me pulsing over your cock like this
my fucking god, it's the first time humans ever made me cum
first like that, I was clinging on your cock
I'm still clenching down at your cock
and you haven't even cum yet
look, Look at the fucking mess I've made all over you
and your cock
You're fucking amazing
You don't even fucking know how goddamn amazing you are
More
I need more
And I need you to come, too
You've done so fucking well so far
Better than anyone I've ever fucked in my life
Okay
I'm just going to turn around
Oh, I can ride you even better this way
make you really fucking hit my cervix
cuz I can tell you love that feeling
and I fucking love it too
and that's how I need you to come
slamming that cock and coming straight against my cervix, just very false
deep
Okay, I'll turn around
I don't even need to slide out of you to do it
mmm, so slick I can let it just slide so easily
All right
There
Now watch me
Watch the ass of your succubus rise and fall over your cock
That's it
That's fucking it
It feels even better this way, doesn't it
Can you see it
Just how much my pussy's already creamed all over your cock
That was you
That was all you You
You made me do all of that
Fuck, it's so good
Fucking soft and so wet and sensitive
but I just can't fucking stop
Do you like it
Do you like watching the ass of your succubus rise and fall on your cock
Oh, yes
I'm yours
I'm fucking yours
No one will ever satisfy me the way you do
There's no way I'm ever fucking anyone else
You're it
You're the only one I'll ever want to fuck
Hey
Do you see my tail
Grab it Yes, yes
I'm sure Grab it, please
as hard as you can Please, I'm going to speed up
Oh my god
You're grabbing it so hard Thank you
thank you
My tail is my erogenous zone Tails are erogenous zone
Like the erogenous zone And you're fucking manhandling it like you own it
Because you do I'm all yours I'll do anything you want
I don't want anything as long as I get you and let's go
Just keep holding on tight
just like that Oh fuck, fuck
I can't really stand it
Why am I making your cock hit my cervix like that
The way you're grabbing my fucking tail
it feels like I'm going to break
Like, my body and mind are going to fucking melt
Oh god
your cock is swelling up and stretching me even more
You're close to coming, aren't you
I don't know if I can take it
You have to come, fill me
fill me up and mark me for life
Cause I can't take much more
I feel like I'm going to fucking break and cum at the same time Fuck
Oh, I don't even care I wanna cum, I wanna break
I just wanna fucking cum and slam my ass down as hard as I can
Cum, cum, I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming
I'm cumming Please cum with me
please cum and slam me
Make me, and mic me
mic me and get me
I want it all
all of you Please, please
please
oh my
god, i
can't believe i came that hard
forget me never having come that hard in my life
I've never seen any other succubus come that hard in my life
Oh my god
You're amazing
I know you're only human, but to me
you're something more
So much more
Calling you a virgin was nothing short of an insult
And I am so sorry for ever calling you that
just look at what you did to me
how much of your cum is dripping out of me
i could just feel your cock pulsing and
spasming in my pussy as i was cumming on it
i'm yours, i'm yours to do whatever you want with
i'll go home and live with you
or you can stay here and live with the brothel with me
whatever you want, i'll do it
but please, i cannot ever let go of you
i am never letting go of you
i can't let go of you
i
couldn't, even if i wanted to you
You see the markings that appeared on my belly
That only appears when a succubus has completely given themselves over to their mate
and only happens when the person mating with the succubus wants her
It means I'm bound to you
For life
You can tell me to do anything
Anything you wanted
and I would gladly follow it
Sorry
to kind of spring bring that on you
Normally
it's something that would require just extraordinary circumstances to happen
Maybe once or twice
every generation in the family line of a succubus hits an incredible honor
Succubi spent their whole lives fucking people
secretly hoping and secretly longing that
they'll see the symbol appear on their belly someday
and most never do
but I have, and you did it to me
You have no idea how happy this makes me
how long I've needed this
It just makes me so happy that you're happy about it, too
It seems we've attracted
attracted quite a crowd outside
Any succubus in the house would have sensed the marking happen to me
and they probably want to get a good look at the man who did it
A taste of the man who did it
They're going to be so jealous when they see my mark
They're probably going to beg you to try and mark them too
even if the odds of them being marked as well would be impossible
But, you are my master
so if you want to spend the rest of the
night fucking and making them more jealous
listening to the sounds we make
or if you want to let one or two of them join in
I'll be elated either way
Whatever it is you want, master, Dear husband
you will have it